1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser("")
29. navigateToUrl(URL)
33. maximizeWindow()
37. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
41. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
45. setText(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), "IPHONE 11 PRO 128 GB DEEP PURPLE")
49. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
53. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-11-pro"))
57. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product"))
61. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
65. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
69. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
73. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
77. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
81. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), 10)
85. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), randomEmail)
89. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/btn_continue"))
93. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), 10)
97. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
101. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
105. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_mobile phone"), randomPhone)
109. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Address"), randomAddress)
113. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
117. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Province"))
121. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
125. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Select Province"))
129. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Khan Chamkar Mon_Select_Province"))
133. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Districts"))
137. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Sangkat Tonle Basak_Districts"))
141. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-save"))
145. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Online Payment - WeChat"))
149. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Checkbox__I accept"))
153. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
157. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/iframe_payment_online"), 7)
161. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/iframe_payment_online"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
165. delay(10)
169. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Approve"))
173. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Continue shopping"), 10)
177. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Continue shopping"), 0)
181. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Continue shopping"))
185. takeScreenshot()
189. comment("Email      : " + randomEmail)
193. comment("First Name : " + randomFirstName)
197. comment("Last Name  : " + randomLastName)
201. comment("Phone      : " + randomPhone)
205. comment("Address    : " + randomAddress)
209. comment("Code    : " + randomCode)
213. takeScreenshot()
217. closeBrowser()